export const response = '[{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 1","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 2","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 3","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 4","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 5","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 6","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 7","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 8","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 9","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 10","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 11","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 12","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 13","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 14","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 15","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 16","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 17","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 18","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 19","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 20","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 21","answer":"Debt","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 22","answer":"Too Ugly","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 23","answer":"Too Fat","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]},{"subject": "Principles of Accounts","chapter":"7","subchapter":"Bankruptcy","type":"1","question":"Why does it happen? 24","answer":"Too Many Hats","options":["Debt","Too Ugly","Too Fat","Too Many Hats"]}]';

export const prepareQuestions = function(props){
    
    props.unsetQuestion();

    var json = JSON.parse(response);
    var getQuestion = json[Math.floor(Math.random()*json.length)];
    props.setQuestion(getQuestion);
    
    return props;
};

//{"subject":"science","chapter":"12. No","type":2,"question":"What is?","answer":["Yes","Statement","Brushless"]}